# Kunal Chandan

Computer Engineering Student

#### **About**

11 Four Winds Dr 14 M3J 1K7 Toronto, ON

kunalthechandan -@gmail.com kunalchandan.github.io Cell: (647)-785-1313

#### Languages

Bilingual English & Hindi Limited French

#### **Programming**

Java Python OpenCV-Octave/MATLAB PsychToolbox-HTML & JavaScript LaTeX

#### Interests

I take heavy interest in computer science, mainly in statistical analysis and machine learning. I first learned to program with Java in 2015, since then I have been improving my skills now I have some experience with Keras, Octave, and OpenCV. I also lead Northview's FIRST robotics team and the programming team.

#### **Education**

2018–2023 Expected Computer Engineering Degree
Honours Computer Engineering Co-op. Starting September of 2018

2014–2018 Ontario Secondary School Diploma
Specialist High Skills Major; Information Computer Tech. (SHSM - ICT)
Honours in Math, Science and Technology (HMST)

# **Experience**

July '17-Curr. Elder Lab, York University

Research Internship.

Computer Vision, Machine Learning, and Psychophysics

-Learning to design neural networks for application in various projects i.e. Traffic tracking, hockey puck tracking

-Writing machine learning algorithms in Java, and Python using Keras and Tensorflow

-Writing scripts using Python and OpenCV for data augmentation and various libraries for data visualization and interpretation

-MATLAB and PsychToolbox for designing psychophysics experiments -Designing methods to gather crowd-sourced data with Amazon MTurk

July–Aug '17 Camp NAORCA, City of Toronto Camp Counsellor.

Voted Rookie of the year; outdoor youth summer camp

2017-2018 FIRST Team 6632, Supreme Robotics Build Executive

Lead and coordinated Supreme Robotics' build team

Jan '18 Northview Heights Secondary School Lead Programming Mentor

Mentored Northview's Co-Ed and All-girls programming teams

2016-2018 Private Tutoring Math & Science Tutor

Tutored children in math and science at local libraries.

# **Applications**

2017–Curr. Personal Website kunalchandan.github.io

Various JavaScript applets, web-toys, and 3D Rendering done with Blender

2017-Curr. Various Psychophysics Experiments Research Internship related work

Designed and programmed psychophysics experiments similar to current re-

search in the Elder Lab

### Other Extra-Curriculars

2014-Curr. Academic Clubs

-Programming Club Founder -Biology Club Executive -Physics Club Member -Math Team Member -DECA Chapter Executive -SHSM-ICT President

-FIRST Robotics Build Executive

2014–Curr. Sports Clubs

-Cross Country Coach/Member

-Badminton Member -Water Polo Member

-Track & Field Coach/Member

## **Awards**

2014-Curr. Academic Awards

-Co-op Award for Outstanding Achievement - Grade 12

-Business Award - Grade 9 & 10 -Honour Roll - All Semesters

-University of Toronto National Biology Competition Scholar Award - Grade

12

-CCC Junior 1st place Northview - Grade 11

-ECOO Round 2 Finalist - Grade 11

-Toronto Finalist for Office Skills Competition - Grade 10 -Toronto Finalist for Robotics and Control Systems - Grade 11

2014-Curr. Athletic Awards

-Bronze Medallion for TDSSAA - Cross Country -Silver Medallion for TDSSAA - Track & Field